List<Map<String, dynamic>> championsleagueQuestions = [
  {
    "question": "Which team won the UEFA Champions League in 2023?",
    "options": ["Manchester City", "Real Madrid", "Bayern Munich", "Liverpool"],
    "answer": "Manchester City"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer in the UEFA Champions League?",
    "options": [
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Lionel Messi",
      "Robert Lewandowski",
      "Karim Benzema"
    ],
    "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which club has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
    "options": ["AC Milan", "Barcelona", "Real Madrid", "Liverpool"],
    "answer": "Real Madrid"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who scored the fastest goal in a UEFA Champions League final?",
    "options": [
      "Paolo Maldini",
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Gareth Bale",
      "Karim Benzema"
    ],
    "answer": "Paolo Maldini"
  },
  {
    "question":
        "Which player has the most assists in UEFA Champions League history?",
    "options": [
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Lionel Messi",
      "Ryan Giggs",
      "Xavi Hernandez"
    ],
    "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
  }
];

List<Map<String, dynamic>> premierleagueQuestions = [
  {
    "question": "Which team won the Premier League in 2023?",
    "options": ["Manchester City", "Arsenal", "Manchester United", "Liverpool"],
    "answer": "Manchester City"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer in the Premier League?",
    "options": [
      "Alan Shearer",
      "Wayne Rooney",
      "Thierry Henry",
      "Sergio Agüero"
    ],
    "answer": "Alan Shearer"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which manager has won the most Premier League titles?",
    "options": [
      "Arsène Wenger",
      "Pep Guardiola",
      "Alex Ferguson",
      "José Mourinho"
    ],
    "answer": "Alex Ferguson"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which club has won the most Premier League titles?",
    "options": ["Manchester United", "Liverpool", "Chelsea", "Arsenal"],
    "answer": "Manchester United"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who scored the fastest hat-trick in Premier League history?",
    "options": [
      "Sadio Mané",
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Wayne Rooney",
      "Thierry Henry"
    ],
    "answer": "Sadio Mané"
  }
];

List<Map<String, dynamic>> laligaQuestions = [
  {
    "question": "Which team won the La Liga in 2023?",
    "options": ["Real Madrid", "Barcelona", "Atlético Madrid", "Sevilla"],
    "answer": "Barcelona"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer in La Liga?",
    "options": ["Cristiano Ronaldo", "Lionel Messi", "Raúl", "Karim Benzema"],
    "answer": "Lionel Messi"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which club has won the most La Liga titles?",
    "options": ["Real Madrid", "Barcelona", "Atlético Madrid", "Valencia"],
    "answer": "Real Madrid"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who has the most assists in La Liga history?",
    "options": [
      "Xavi Hernandez",
      "Lionel Messi",
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Andrés Iniesta"
    ],
    "answer": "Lionel Messi"
  },
  {
    "question":
        "Which player holds the record for most appearances in La Liga?",
    "options": [
      "Iker Casillas",
      "Lionel Messi",
      "Andoni Zubizarreta",
      "Sergio Ramos"
    ],
    "answer": "Andoni Zubizarreta"
  }
];
